Garden Club of Hartford records
Connecticut Historical Society
Garden Club of Hartford records
1916-
Connecticut Historical Society, Hartford, Connecticut
Garden Club of Hartford
8.5 linear feet (32 boxes)
Historical Sketch
The Garden Club of Hartford was founded on March 16, 1916 by eight women: Mrs. James P. Andrews, Miss Frances Beach, Mrs. John H. Buck, Mrs. Albert s. Cook, Miss Bertha Dennis, Mrs. Robert W. Gray, Mrs. Robert W. Huntington, and Mrs. Samuel O. Prentice. Mrs. Prentice was the first President and Mrs. Gray the first Secretary and Treasurer. The initiation fee was $2.00 and dues were $1.00. In 1920 the Garden Club of America (founded 1913) admitted the Hartford club as a member.
The Garden Club of Hartford has been active in the community in civic projects since it’s founding. They have contributed their time and have raised money to effect their goals of beautification, conservation, promotion of gardening, and scholarships and fellowships. Funds have been raised by plant sales, flea markets, auctions, dances, and publications. The Old State House has been their largest project. The restoration of the Sunken Garden at Hill-Stead Museum was completed in 1988.
The Club has grown from eight original members to 62 active members in 1988, with 29 members in other categories. Meetings are still held at members houses as originally conceived, as well as at arboretums and other places of interest to learn about such things as plant propagation, pest control, pruning, etc. Members visit fellow members’ gardens, enter and attend flower shows, and keep active in the community.
Scope and Content
The records are arranged in ten series. Series I consists of organizational records including articles of incorporation, tax exempt certificates, and minutes of meetings. Series II contains records of projects and awards. These include civic projects, flower shows, etc. The Club’s publications are organized in Series III while photographs can be found in Series IV. In consecutive order, the final series contain clippings and scrapbooks; questionnaires and answers; miscellaneous materials; records and publications of the Federated Garden Clubs of Connecticut; records and publications of the Garden Club of America; and notices, circulars and other published materials from assorted gardening organizations.
The arrangement is chronological. The minutes in Series I contain supplemental material relating to the year’s activities, including correspondence, financial statements, and issues of the Trumpet Vine. The Club continues to add to this collection as they purge inactive files. Additions are added in new boxes after the last numbered box. No attempt is made to integrate new materials into those already processed. However, the new materials are organized into the same Series and are arranged chronologically.
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions on access to the collection.
Accruals
The collection is open. Additional material is expected.
Subject Headings
Subjects
Gardening -- Societies, etc.; Women -- Societies and clubs.
Contents:
- I. Basic Organizational Records
  - Constitution and by-laws (Box 1, Folder A1)
  - Admission and project policy, guidelines for Executive Committee members (Box 1, Folder A2)
  - Tax Exempt number, Certificate of Incorporation Information (Box 1, Folder A3)
  - Minutes, 1916 (Box 1, Folder B1)
  - Minutes, 1917 (Box 1, Folder B2)
  - Minutes, 1918 (Box 1, Folder B3)
  - Minutes, 1919 (Box 1, Folder B4)
  - Minutes, 1920 (Box 1, Folder B5)
  - Minutes, 1921 (Box 1, Folder B6)
  - Minutes, 1922 (Box 1, Folder B7)
  - Minutes, 1923 (Box 1, Folder B8)
  - Minutes, 1924 (Box 1, Folder B9)
  - Minutes, 1925 (Box 1, Folder B10)
  - Minutes, 1926 (Box 1, Folder B11)
  - Minutes, 1927 (Box 1, Folder B12)
  - Minutes, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder B13)
  - Minutes, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder B14)
  - Minutes, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder B15)
  - Minutes, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder B16)
  - Minutes, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder B17)
  - Minutes, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder B18)
  - Minutes, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder B19)
  - Minutes, 1935 (Box 1, Folder B20)
  - Minutes, 1936 (Box 1, Folder B21)
  - Minutes, 1937 (Box 1, Folder B22)
  - Minutes, 1938 (Box 1, Folder B23)
  - Minutes, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder B24)
  - Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder B25)
  - Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder B26)
  - Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder B27)
  - Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder B28)
  - Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder B29)
  - Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder B30)
  - Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder B31)
  - Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder B32)
  - Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder B33)
  - Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder B34)
  - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder B35)
  - Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder B36)
  - Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder B37)
  - Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder B38)
  - Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder B39)
  - Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder B40)
  - Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder B41)
  - Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder B42)
  - Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder B43)
  - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder B44)
  - Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder B45)
  - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder B46)
  - Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder B47)
  - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder B48)
  - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder B49)
  - Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder B50)
  - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder B51)
  - Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder B52)
  - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder B53)
  - Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder B54)
  - Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder B55)
  - Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder B56)
  - Minutes, 1971-1972; (Trumpet Vine begins) (Box 4, Folder B57)
  - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder B58)
  - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder B59)
  - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder B60)
  - Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder B61)
  - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder B62)
  - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder B63)
  - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder B64)
  - Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder B65)
  - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder B66)
  - Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder B67)
  - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder B68)
  - Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder B69)
  - Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder B70)
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder B71)
  - Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder B72)
  - Financial statements, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder C)
  - Trumpet Vine, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder D)
  - Annual Reports of Custodians, 1973-1986 (Box 6, Folder E)
  - English Garden Pilgrimage, 1929 (Box 6, Folder F)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence including Tributes, 1954-1977 (Box 6, Folder G)
  - Histories and Reviews, 1939 (Box 6, Folder H)
  - 25th Anniversary, 1941 (Box 6, Folder I)
  - 50th Anniversary, 1966 (Box 6, Folder J)
  - 50th Anniversary celebration, 1966 (Box 6, Folder K)
  - History, 1972 (Box 6, Folder L)
  - History, 1963-1985 (Box 6, Folder M)
  - Committee Assignments of Members, 1916-1975 (Box 6, Folder N)
  - Review, 1988 (Box 6, Folder O)
  - History of Pewter Bowl Award, 1953 (Box 6, Folder P)
  - Tax exemptions, 1965-1967, 1990; copy of certificate of incorporation, 1965. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - President or secretary’s notebook, 1981-1982. Includes committee reports, newsletter the Trumpet Vine, and correspondence from other gardening organizations. In reverse chronological order. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - President’s or Secretary’s notebook, 1986-1988. Includes minutes of Executive Committee meetings, reports, newsletter the Trumpet Vine, minutes of annual meetings. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Notice of Long-range Planning meeting, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - President’s or Secretary’s file, 1996-1997. Includes photographs. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Recording Secretary’s notebook, May 1988-May 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Recording Secretary’s notebook, May 1992-May 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Nina Stanley bequest, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Committee descriptions, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - New member handbook, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Member information and obituaries, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Annual reports, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Historian and Scholarship Committee reports, 1996, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of meetings, September 1994-May 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Secretary’s notebook, September 1996-May 1998. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Secretary’s notebook, 1998-2001. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 2003-2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Member’s handbook, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Biographical information about Virginia Miller (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, clippings, 1975, 1981-1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Assorted historical materials (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Secretary’s notebook, 2002-2004 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Secretary’s notebook, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 2006-2008 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Annual reports, 1960, 1993-2006 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Annual reports, 2001-2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Annual reports, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Annual reports, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Membership information (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Board minutes, 2008-April 2012 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Regular meeting minutes, May 2008-April 2012 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Annual report, 2009-2010 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Annual report, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Annual report, 2011-2012 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Historian's notebook, 2001-2010 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Information on deceased members, 2007-2012 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence relating to "Much Ado About Gardening" (Box 30, Folder 8)
- II. Projects and Awards
  - Trinity College, 1938 (Box 7, Folder A)
  - Projects, 1958-1965; (see two sketches for planters on Main Street in Oversize Box) (Box 7, Folder B)
  - Hartford College for Women, 1960 (Box 7, Folder C)
  - Old State House, 1960 (Box 7, Folder D)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1965; (three sketches in Oversize Box) (Box 7, Folder E)
  - Children's Museum, 1968 (Box 7, Folder F)
  - Mark Twain House, 1969 (Box 7, Folder G)
  - Burgdorf Health Center, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder H)
  - Conservation New Letter, 1975 (Box 7, Folder I)
  - Old State House, 1978 (Box 7, Folder J)
  - Old State House Agreement, Rededication, Clippings, Award Proposal (1978), Award (Box 7, Folder K)
  - Old State House Gala and Auction, 1978 (Box 7, Folder L)
  - Old State House Raffle (Box 7, Folder M)
  - Founders Fund Award Proposal for Old State House (Box 7, Folder N)
  - Award Proposals 1981-1983, Misc Awards (Box 7, Folder O)
  - Bushnell Park, 1984 (Box 7, Folder P)
  - Hill-Stead Garden Market and Gala, 1986 (Box 7, Folder Q)
  - Civic Projects, 1972-1989. Committee records, budget, correspondence, newspaper clippings (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Medal from Garden Club of America, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Civic Project, Hartford College for Women, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Bushnell Park restoration project, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hill-Stead Sunken Garden project, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Information and slides of Butler McCook garden, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Information and slides of Elizabeth Park, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Nature’s Palette flower show, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Civic Projects, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Civic Projects, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Children’s Medical Center project, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jubilee House, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hill-Stead Garden Market and Sunken Garden Project, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Legislative workshop audiotape, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Nature’s Palette flower show, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation Award, from Garden Club of America, 1992; (oversize) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Knox Park Foundation Greenhouse Project, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Community Garden Project, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Auction at Kitty Smiths, Farmington, 1995; (photographs) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 80th Anniversary celebration, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Mary Hooker School Project, ca. 1996; (photographs) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Arbor Day, 2000; (photographs) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 2000, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Corning Fountain Project, Bushnell Park, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Pope Park 1000 Daffodils Project, 2002; (photographs) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Report on Pope Park Project, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Program booklets, 2004-2008 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Program flyers, 1996, 2005-2008 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 90th Birthday minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 90th Birthday final report, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Fishers Island excursion, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Arbor Day, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 90th Birthday committee minutes, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 80th Birthday, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - President’s report, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1992-2006 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board minutes, 1998-2006 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Secretary’s duties, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Civic project report update, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Bushnell Park civic project, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Awards, 1981, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Flower show, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Old State House civic project, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Perennial fund, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - South Green/Barnard Park civic project, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Pope Park civic project (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Members (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Membership—Corresponding Secretary reports, 1978-2002 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Membership—attendance records (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Membership records (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Publicity (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Name placards, invitation, napkins, favor, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Publicity, toast made at party, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Knox Park, 1990-1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 80th Anniversary booklet and celebration, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Bushnell Park/Corning Fountain, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Corning Fountain, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Christmas auction, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 90th Anniversary booklet (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - GCH Garden History and Design Committee submission to the Archives of American Gardens, Smithsonian (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Awards, 2008, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Holiday auction, 2009, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Stowe Center rose garden, 2010, and undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
- III. Garden Club of Hartford Publications
  - Garden Tips, 1967; (became "Much Ado About Gardening") (Box 8, Folder A-L)
  - Garden Tips (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Garden Tips (Box 9, Folder N)
  - Correspondence relating to "Much Ado About Gardening,", 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder O)
  - Much Ado About Gardening, 1967 (Box 9, Folder P)
  - Highways and Byways, 1928 (Box 9, Folder Q)
  - Christmas Concoctions, 1975 (Box 9, Folder R)
  - Recipes (Box 9, Folder S)
  - Articles for Garden Club of America Bulletin, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder T)
  - Articles printed in Garden Club of America Bulletin (Box 9, Folder U)
  - Trumpet Vine, September 1990-December 1992 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - “Custodian’s” file. Trumpet Vine, June,1989-June 1990; newspaper stories, 1961, 1988-1989; photographs, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Trumpet Vine, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Trumpet Vine, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Annual brochure/program, 1974-2004 (Box 22, Folder 10-12)
  - Trumpet Vine newsletter, January 2000-January 2005 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1993-2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Trumpet Vine reports, correspondence and mock-ups, 1987-2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tribute to Deb Eddy, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Trumpet Vine, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Trumpet Vine, 2005-2008 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Trumpet Vine, 2008, 2020-2012 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Program booklets, 2008-2012 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 2011 Cookbook (Box 31, Folder 3)
- IV. Photographic Material
  - Snapshots, 1953-1969 (Box 10, Folder A)
  - Snapshots, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder B)
  - Snapshots, 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder C)
  - Snapshots, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder D)
  - Garden Club of Hartford photo 1985, Garden Club of America in Newport, RI in 1923, misc. (Box 10, Folder E)
  - Slides, 1967 (Box 10, Folder F)
  - Slide box (Box 11, Folder G)
  - Black and white slide for lecture (?) (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Possibly members on a garden tour and members repotting plants in someone’s backyard, no date (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Greens Workshop, Hill-Stead Museum, December 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Meeting at Deb Eddy’s, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Visiting gardens, August 2001. Gardens of Joan Brown, Noank; Sandy Fromson, Stonington; and Gay Wagner, Hampton (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Corning Fountain, Bushnell Park, Spring 2003 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Garden Stroll, Betty Stanley’s house, Canton, September 2004 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Flower show, Gwen Izard’s house, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Flower show, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Zone meeting, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 2004 activities (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 2004 workshops (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Jubilee House plantings, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 80th Birthday celebration, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 90th Birthday and other 2006 events (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - CDs with photographic images (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, ca. 1985-2000, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 90th anniversary, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Various projects, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 2008-2010 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
- V. Clippings and Scrapbooks
  - Clippings (Box 12, Folder A)
  - Scrapbook (Oversize), 1924-1978
  - Scrapbook (Oversize), 1979-1986
  - Clippings, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- VI. Questionaires and Answers
  - 1965 (Box 12, Folder A)
  - 1969 (Box 12, Folder B)
  - 1972 (Box 12, Folder C)
  - 1976 (Box 12, Folder D)
- VII. Miscellaneous
  - Misc. data, not dated (Box 13, Folder A)
  - Media in Connecticut (Box 13, Folder B)
  - Air Quality Standards in Connecticut (Box 13, Folder C)
  - Apron from 1920s Flower Marts (Oversize)
  - Newsletter, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Garden guides, 1953, 1976; annual report, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Zone II meeting, May 1993 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Eco-Exchange at Garden Club of America annual meeting, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Zone II annual meeting, June 2000 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Zone II annual meeting, 2000, photographs of boat trip (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Zone II annual meeting, June 2003 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Zone II annual meeting, June 2000, steering committee records (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Zone II annual meeting, brochures, name badges, other souveniers, June 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Zone II annual meeting, committee reports, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Zone II annual meeting, June 2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Centennial information, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Brochure, and Bulletin, 2011-2012 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- VIII. Federated Garden Clubs of Connecticut
  - Publications, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Zone II meeting, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Connecticut plants (Box 32, Folder 7)
- IX. Garden Club of America
  - Policy and Bylaws (Box 14, Folder A)
  - Handbook (Box 14, Folder B)
  - Zoning (Box 14, Folder C)
  - Annual Meetings, 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder D)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1981 (Box 14, Folder E)
  - Yearbook, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder F)
  - Flower Show/Judging Guide, 1953, 1954, 1961, 1963, 1970, 1978 (Box 14, Folder G)
  - Flower Shows/Exhibiting, 1924, 1925, 1927, 1973 (Box 15, Folder H)
  - Awards (Box 15, Folder I)
  - Activities/Histories, 1913-1938 (Box 15, Folder J)
  - Membership in Connecticut, 1938 (Box 15, Folder K)
  - Library (Box 15, Folder L)
  - Political Action (Box 15, Folder M)
  - Members Gardens, 1921, 1922, 1924 (Box 15, Folder N)
  - Almanac, 1924, 1925, 1926 (Box 15, Folder O)
  - Bulletin, 1934, 1936, 1966, 1968, 1976, 1979 (Box 15, Folder P)
  - Bulletin, 1978, 1980, 1981 (Box 15, Folder Q)
  - Visiting Gardens Guide, 1967 (Box 15, Folder R)
- X. Miscellaneous Bodies
  - National Council of State Garden Clubs (Box 16, Folder A)
  - Farmington River and Watershed Guide (Box 16, Folder B)
  - Bartholomew's Cobble (Box 16, Folder C)
  - Pine Acres Forest (Box 16, Folder D)
  - Olive W. Lee Memorial Garden (Box 16, Folder E)
  - Arnold Arboretum (Box 16, Folder F)
  - Connecticut Arboretum (Box 16, Folder G)
  - New York Botanical Garden (Box 16, Folder H)
  - Operation Triangle, Seattle, WA (Box 16, Folder I)
  - Pine Acres Farm (Box 16, Folder J)
  - The Conservationist (Box 16, Folder K)
  - Quarantine Act, 1919 (Box 16, Folder L)
  - Garden Center of Greater Cleveland Bulletin (Box 16, Folder M)
  - Connecticut Horticultural Society (Box 16, Folder N)
  - Garden Club of Evanston, IL paper (Box 16, Folder O)
  - Garden Club of New Haven color chart (Box 16, Folder P)
  - Lennox Bicentennial Flower Show (Box 16, Folder Q)
  - Governor of Oregon address (Box 16, Folder R)
  - Student Conservation Association of Charlestown, NH report (Box 16, Folder S)
  - Farmington Garden club Fact Finding Committee report (Box 16, Folder T)
  - A Primer on Air Pollution (Box 16, Folder U)
  - Greenwich Garden Club 50th Anniversary program (Box 16, Folder V)
  - Misc. materials (Box 16, Folder W)